flexithemes.com 2011-06-08

# Privacy Policy | FlexiThemes

Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information from that point forward; and not on a retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

**Collection of Information**  
We automatically collect personally identifiable information, like names, IP addresses, postal addresses, email addresses, etc… from you when you visit our web site. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors use and navigate our web pages on an aggregate basis. This information is used only for our internal web trends analysis, and is never published or used to identify you in any way. When you fill in our forms to sign up, we record your name, and the contact information you provide to us. This information is retained indefinitely by Multisite Manager, and is used to keep you informed about our products and services. It is never sold, rented or leased to any third party.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology**  
This site may use cookie and tracking technology, depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

**Distribution of Information**  
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

**Commitment to Data Security**  
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
